CARLA POMARICO

Sr. QA Engineer

Argentinian, married - 28.07.1986 Balvanera, Buenos Aires, AR Mobile (+54911) 64763655 carpomarico@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carla-pomarico

WORK EXPERIENCE

Morean (Evolv.ai), AR: Sr. QA Engineer

11.2021 - Present

Non-functional web testing (visual, layout, design, mkt metrics). JIRA. XRay. AGILE (Scrum, Kanban). Confluence. Visual Studio code. Working on STG & Production environments).

Yappa Inc., USA (remote): Sr. QA Engineer

08.2020 - 10.2021

Functional web and mobile testing. TestRail. JIRA. Confluence. Figma. Postman. API RESTFUL. SauceLabs. Passbolt. ExpressVPN. AWS.

Morean (FWI), AR: Sr. QA Engineer

02.2020 - 08.2020

Functional and non-functional web and mobile testing. PractiTest. AGILE (Scrum, Kanban). JIRA. Confluence. Github. Visual Studio code. Working on DEV, STG & Production environments. Postman. API RESTFUL. AWS, DynamoDB. MongoDB (Robomongo 3T). Zephyr for JIRA. First training in test automation with Java, Selenium and Cucumber with Gherkin. Intellij & Github. BrowserStack.

OLX Group, AR: Sr. QA Engineer

12.2019 - 02.2020

Functional and non-functional testing. Visual Studio (TFS). JIRA. Confluence. Gitlab. Visual Studio code. Android Studio. AGILE (Scrum, Kanban). Cucumber with Gherkin. Postman. Jmeter. SQL. API RESTFUL. Udemy Certifications: UML & OOP, Introduction to HTML & CSS, Introduction to Javascript.

Yoizen S.A., AR: Sr. QA Analyst

02.2018 - 12.2019

Functional and non-functional testing. Visual Studio (TFS). Working on DEV, QA and Production environments. Progress Telerik Fiddler. Github. Webstorm. Trello. JIRA. Freshdesk. Customer Technical support. Logs analysis. Technical writing. Release notes. User manuals redaction & correction. On-site / remote training in the use of company's products for customers. On-site / remote application's knowledge transfer for new customers. Functional analysis: survey of clients, design of use cases, user stories, assembly of functional documentation formalizing the client's requirements.

AYNOU, AR: Ssr. QA Analyst/Functional Analyst

03.2017 - 02-2018

Functional and non-functional testing. Microsoft Test Manager. First approach to automation testing via Sikulix and Katalon Studio. Microsoft SQL Server. Functional documentation analysis. Smoke testing. Trello. AGILE methodology (Scrum). Functional analysis: survey of clients, design of use cases, user stories, assembly of functional documentation formalizing the client's requirements.

Wunderman, AR: QA/QC Analyst (temporary job)

03.2016 - 10.2016

Content and functional testing on web and mobile. JIRA. Trello. AGILE Methodology: Scrum. **Project: Ford USA & Canada - Lincoln USA**

Freelance, AR: QA Analyst

07.2013 - 02.2016

Functional & non functional testing of web apps. ERP Émerix. JIRA. Testlink. Trello. SQL Server & MySQL (basic). Waterfall & AGILE (Scrum) methodologies. *Some projects: Banco Estado (CL), Banco Hipotecario, Personal, República Microfinanzas (UY).*

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native English - Advanced Russian - Basic Portuguese - Basic

EDUCATION

Social Communication 08.2020 - Present - I.S.T.L.y R.

Spanish and literature professorship 03.2008 - 07.2017 - I.E.S. N° 1

Systems analyst 03.2018 - 12.2018 - I.FT.S. N° 5

History 04.2005 - 11.2007 - UBA

ABOUT ME

I am a very restless and curious person. I love challenges and I am by nature self-taught and autonomous. However, I have an excellent management of interpersonal relationships. I love working as a team and I like to share my knowledge with the groups in which I am. Also, I am always interested in learning more to develop and grow both personally and professionally. After having started as a freelance QA and worked in several projects, today I have more than 8 years of IT experience.